### Daniel Ogunseye

+44 (0) 7593352851 | danielogunseye@gmail.com

A high-preforming and enthusiastic computer science graduate from Oxford Brookes University. I have developed my skills in Python, Agile and Machine Learning. My competitive nature instils in me the drive to research and develop valuable skill sets which enables me to collaborate more effectively with the team. My problem-solving ability allows me to navigate through the complexity of a given task providing the root of the problem and proposing a viable solution.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Earnest Marketing Agency – Digital Marketing (Internship)**

Jun - Jul 2021

- I worked with the head of marketing and other senior representatives from different departments in the agency.
- This enabled me to gain valuable insights to the world of B2B marketing and digital marketing.
- I engaged in client service meetings with current and potential clients of the agency.
- I worked on the annual Spotify 2021 Wrapped Campaign, offering innovative ways for Spotify to monetise the data generated through this campaign by selling it to the top 200 advertising spenders.
- I gave a presentation about the Spotify Wrapped campaign for the year 2021. This campaign included a variety of features that are relevant to a wide range of Spotify users worldwide.

### **BLACK VALLEY MENTORSHIP GRADUATE**

April 2021 - Jun 2021

- A mentee at the Black Valley mentorship program where I was mentored by Lee Hilton Smith, a Cloud Solution Architect at Microsoft.
- I worked with my mentor to develop skills and experience in data science, focusing on Microsoft Azure ML in order to progress towards a career in data science.
- I am developing my knowledge and familiarity with Microsoft Azure since starting the program thus motivating me to take the DP-100 certification exam in the near future.

### **FUTURE YOUTH ZONE - YOUTH WORKER**

May 2019 - Present

- As a youth sports worker, I am responsible for planning and organising youth and community programs to engage young people.
- Liaising with parents and youth workers to establish learning objectives.
- Organised a summer basketball event for over 30 students. Used event as a vehicle to promote team and leadership skills amongst young people.

### **AFWS CLOTHING - LONDON**

May 2019 - Present

- I created AFWS clothing as community driven clothing brand which focuses on teaching the positive aspects of black history through clothing.
- The media tends to solely base black history around slavery, so the inspiration is to shift that narrative and highlight the greatness of black history through fashionable clothing.
- Encourages the community to learn the inspiration behind the clothing designs thus giving 60% of profits to charitable causes.
- My University provided an opportunity by working with Santander University and creating a platform where start-up businesses can pitch for some funding.

# TROUNCEFLOW-LONDON DATA ANALYST (Internship)

Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

- I worked with senior analysts to evaluate and adjust work procedures for optimum efficiency.
- I prepared reports by gathering, analysing and summarising data on the substantial inflow of foreign holdings in the emerging markets.
- I used Jupyter Notebook to import python libraries such as NumPy and Pandas to clean and manipulate large datasets, which were used in the daily emails sent to clients thus providing a clearer insight on investors behaviours.
- I delivered presentations needed to follow up on specific leads, whilst collaborating with data and quant teams.
- I engaged in regular client meetings to obtain a deeper insight into business activities.
- The key skills I developed during this internship includes an in-depth understanding of emerging markets as well as using python to analyse financial dataset and sending daily emails to keep the clients updated on investors behaviours in the financial market.

- I was responsible for analysing student application forms to confirm the applicant's eligibility to attend the University.
- Provided general administrative support, including co-ordination and distribution of agendas, supporting documents, producing and distributing minutes, and follow-ups on outstanding actions.
- Acted as first point of contact for staff and students and responsible for resolving a wide range of gueries.
- Gained strong organisational skills with the ability to handle and prioritise several tasks.
- Strong team player and a proven ability to work pro-actively.

## **ARC AGENCY TEAM LEADER**

Jul 2017 - December 2018

- I worked as a Team Leader at Wembley Stadium and London Stadium overseeing their bar services.
- I was responsible for setting and enforcing quality and hygiene standards and making improvements to the general running and efficiency of the bar.
- I created an environment oriented to trust and open communication with the staff members and the customers.
- I managed a team of 5 bar staff and helped develop good leadership skills as well as crucial customer service skills.

### POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY & VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE

- I actively participated in a community outreach programme run by the Faulkner basketball team, Jun 2016 Jul 2016 where I engaged basketball camp attendees in a variety of drills and led various team talks before games to ensure children remained enthusiastic and motivated.
- Acted in role model capacity for several elementary school students and participated in several activities to promote higher aspirations and future career progression.

EDUCATION		
<b>BSc</b> Computer Science	Oxford Brookes University, Upper Second-Class Honours (2:1)	2017 - 2020
Faulkner University	US Basketball Scholarship	2016 - 2017
Seminole State College	US Basketball Scholarship	2015 - 2016
A Levels: Barking	Biology (C), Chemistry (C), Psychology (B)	2011 - 2014
Abbey Sixth Form		
GCSEs: St	9 A - C including R.E (A) English (B), Mathematics (B), Science (B) St Bonaventure's School	
<b>Bonaventure's School</b>		2009 - 2011
Eastlea Community		2006 - 2009
School		

## **INTERESTS & ACHIEVEMENTS**

### **SOCIETY - ICE QUBE INNOVATION HUB**

- Active member of ICE Qube at Oxford Brookes University which provided a space for start-up businesses in need of expert advice and mentors.
- I networked with seasoned entrepreneurs and mentors who provided a deeper insight into the business world.

## **KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**

EDUCATION

- Winner of Spark and Fuel Award pitch of £3,250.
- Member of the England U18 basketball team.
- Winner of Newham All-Star Sports Academy (NASSA) Most improved player award which was presented in the House of Parliament.
- Qualified level 3 basketball coach.

Languages English (native) | Yoruba (fluent) | French (Learning/Beginner).

Interests Basketball | Podcast | Food | Fashion | Travelling | Chess | Gym | Adventure.